Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Digests of Cases (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters v. C.A. Dodge. Cambridge, MA, 127 (Reel 22)
  - Timbermen v. Warsaw Southern Lumber Company. Laurel, MS, 128 (Reel 22)
  - Metal Mine Workers v. Silver Bow Employers Association. Butte, MT, 129 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Employers. Cleveland, OH, 130 (Reel 22)
  - Molders v. Canton Steel Foundry. Canton, OH, 131 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Employers. Kokomo, IN, 132 (Reel 22)
  - Foundrymen v. Grey Iron Club. Brooklyn, NY, 133 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Putnam Machine. Fitchburg, MA., 134 (Reel 22)
  - Textile Workers v. Lowell Mill Treasurers. Lowell, MA, 135 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 817 et al. v. Columbus Railway, Power, and Light. Columbus, OH, 136 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Jackson and Church et al. Saginaw, MI., 137 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Jersey City Machinery. Jersey City, NJ, 138 (Reel 22)
  - Master Roofers Association v. Naval Station et al. Boston, MA and Vicinity, 139 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 806, 810, and 749 v. City Railway et al. Dayton, OH, 140 (Reel 22)
  - Inquiry of City Button Works. New York City. Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 623 v. International Railway. Buffalo, NY., 141 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 350 v. Schoelkopf Chemical. Buffalo, NY, 142 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 807 v. Omaha and Council Bluffs Street Railway. Omaha, NE., 143 (Reel 22)
  - Oil and Gas Well Workers, Local 15503 v. Employers. Taft, CA., 144 (Reel 22)
  - Brotherhood of Drop Forge Trades v. Remington Arms et al. Bridgeport, CT, 145 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 196 v. United Engineering. Youngstown, OH., 146 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Triangle Pattern and Manufacturing et al. Detroit, MI., 147 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 732 v. Georgia Railway and Power. Atlanta, GA., 148 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 196 v. United Engineering. Youngstown, OH., 149 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Triangle Pattern and Manufacturing et al. Detroit, MI., 150 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 732 v. Georgia Railway and Power. Atlanta, GA., 151 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 81 v. A.F. Brown et al. Elizabethtown, NJ., 152 (Reel 22)
  - Envelope, Paper Box, and Paper Bag Association v. Samuel Cupples Envelope Company. St. Louis, MO, 153 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Employers. East Providence, RI, 154 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists et al. v. Worthington Pump and Machinery. Cudahy, WI., 155 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. Fox Brothers Manufacturing et al. St. Louis, MO, 156 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 164 v. Wilkes-Barre Railway, 157 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Corn Products Company. Argo, IL, 158 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland and Eastern Traction. Cleveland, OH, 159 (Reel 22)
  - Painters, Local 28 v. Cahogan Shipyards et al. Long Island City, NY., 160 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Middletown Car. Middletown, PA, 161 (Reel 22)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers et al. v. National Enameling and Stamping. Granite City, IL and St. Louis, MO., 162 (Reel 22)
  - Auto Tire Builders and Finishers Federal Labor Union 16159 v. Ehman Tire and Rubber. Chicago, IL, 163 (Reel 22)
  - Employers v. Machinists. Akron, OH, 164 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 746 v. Denver City Tramway. Denver, Col, 165 (Reel 22)
  - Federal Labor Union 15047 v. Union Carbide. Sault Ste. Marie, MI., 166 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 805 v. East St. Louis, Columbia, and Waterloo Railway. East St. Louis, IL., 167 (Reel 22)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 601 v. Hammond Packing et al. Pittsburgh and McKeesport, PA., 168 (Reel 22)
  - Metal Trades Council v. Ajax Iron Works et al. Denver, CO., 169 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Joseph Mason Machine. Philadelphia, 170 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 618 v. Rhode Island Company. Providence, RI. Pattern Makers v. Employers. Toledo, OH, 171 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Hannan Slocum Company. Newark, NJ, 172 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Archibald Wheel Company. Lawrence, MA, 173 (Reel 22)
  - Leather Workers v. National Leather Belting et al. New York City, NY., 174 (Reel 22)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute between Iron Workers Union and Plumbers Union. Boston, 175 (Reel 22)
  - Ladies Garment Workers, Local 26, 27, 29, 37, and 42 v. Manufacturers. Cleveland, OH, 176 (Reel 22)
  - Jewelry Workers, Local 18 v. Jewelry manufacturers. Attleboro, MA., 177 (Reel 22)
  - Central Federated Union v. National metal Trades Association. Providence, RI., 178 (Reel 22)
  - Oil and Gas Workers, Local 16107 v. Employers. Martinez, CA, 179 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. American International Shipbuilding et al. Boston, MA, Gloucester, NJ and Philadelphia, PA., 180 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 725 v. Birmingham Railway, Light, and Power. Birmingham, AL., 181 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 268 v. Cleveland, Painesville and Eastern Railway Employees v. Twin City Rapid Transit Company et al. St. Paul, MN, 182 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 761 v. Springfield Consolidated. Springfield, IL, 183 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. American Steel. Franklin, PA, 184 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters v. Imperial Shipbuilding. Detroit, MI, 185 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 55 v. Superior Tool. Columbus, OH, 186 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 524 and 165 v. Northwestern Fuel et al. Superior, WI, 187 (Reel 22)
  - Tobacco Workers v. American Tobacco. Louisville, KY., 188 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 669 v. Auburn and Syracuse Electric Railroad. Auburn, NY, 189 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Metal Trades Employers. Birmingham, AL., 190 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 713 v. Memphis Street Railway. Memphis, TN, 191 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 738 v. Cincinnati and Dayton Traction. Dayton, OH, 192 (Reel 22)
  - Montana Metal Trades v. Anaconda Copper. Great Falls, MT., 193 (Reel 22)
  - Hazel Glass Company v. Employees. Washington, PA and Wheeling, WV, 194 (Reel 22)
  - Federal Employees v. US Navy Department. Washington, DC., 195 (Reel 22)
  - Conductors, Trainmen, and Engineers v. Interurban Lines. Portland, OR, 196 (Reel 22)
  - Stove Mounters, Local 1 v. Michigan Stove et al. Detroit, MI., 197 (Reel 22)
  - Hod Carriers, Local 407 v. US Naval Torpedo Station. Newport, RI, 198 (Reel 22)
  - Colored Bag Men and Mail Porters v. Employers. Philadelphia, PA, 199 (Reel 22)
  - Railroad Trainmen, Local 808 et al. v. Pacific Electric Railway. Los Angeles., 200 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 398 v. American Standard Metal Products. Bordentown, NJ, 201 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters, Local 14 et al. v. Thomas Harmon et al. San Antonio, TX, 202 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Colt Firearms. Hartford, CT., 203 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Charles Perkes. Philadelphia, PA, 204 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Bethlehem Steel. Sparrows Point, MD, 205 (Reel 22)
  - Metal Polishers, Local 2 v. Employers. Toledo, OH, 206 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 161 v. Kleiber-Dawson Machine. Indianapolis, IN., 207 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Lodge 364 v. Holt Manufacturing. Stockton, CA, 208 (Reel 22)
  - Women Employees v. Chevrolet. Bay City, MI, 209 (Reel 22)
  - Federal Labor Unions 16067 and 16135 v. Employers. Madison, WI, 210 (Reel 22)
  - Boilermakers v. American Locomotive. Richmond, VA, 211 (Reel 22)
  - Firefighters v. Municipal Government. Pittsburgh, PA., 212 (Reel 22)
  - Hotel, Restaurant, and Bartenders Organization v. Hotel and Restaurant Employers. Chicago, IL., 213 (Reel 22)
  - Express Drivers v. American Railway Express. Columbus, OH, 214 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 228 v. Chicago and Joliet Electric Railway. Joliet, IL., 215 (Reel 22)
  - Hardwood Finishers, Local 426 et al. v. Manufacturers of Interior Wood Work. Philadelphia, PA., 216 (Reel 22)
  - Lynn Central Labor Union et al. v. General Electric. Lynn, MA., 217 (Reel 22)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. American Sheet and Tin Plate. Elwood, IN., 218 (Reel 22)
  - Inquiry of Warren Steam Pump Company. Warren, MA., 219 (Reel 22)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 468 v. Decker and Sons. Mason City, IA., 220 (Reel 22)
  - Shoe Cutters v. Brockton Shoe Manufacturers. Brockton, MA, 221 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Millville Rubber. Millville, MA, 222 (Reel 22)
  - Railway Conductors, Division 337 v. Washington, Baltimore and Annapolis Electric Railway. Baltimore, MD, 223 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Virginia Bridge and Iron. Memphis, TN, 224 (Reel 22)
  - Employees Association v. Brooklyn Rapid Transit. Brooklyn, NY, 225 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Columbus, Delaware and Marion Electric. Marion, OH, 226 (Reel 22)
  - Boilermakers v. Warren City Tank and Boiler. Toledo, OH, 227 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 335 v. Connersville Blower et al. Connersville, IN., 228 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Eugene Dietzgen. Chicago, 229 (Reel 22)
  - Retail Clerks, Local 424 v. Kroger Grocery. St. Louis, MO, 230 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 737 v. Northern Electric Railway. Syracuse, NY, 231 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 307 v. Morgan Engineering. Alliance, OH., 232 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Transue Williams Steel Forging. Alliance, OH, 233 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Linderman Steel and Machinery. Muskegon, MI., 234 (Reel 22)
  - Toledo Bridge and Crane v. Employees. Toledo, OH, 235 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 767 v. Knoxville Railway and Light. Knoxville, TN, 236 (Reel 22)
  - Molders v. Hurley machine. Chicago, IL, 237 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Zenith System. Tonawanda, NY, 238 (Reel 22)
  - Mechanics v. Steel Ship Link Belt. Chicago, IL., 239 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Consolidated Car Heating. NA, 240 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Astoria Gas, Light and Heat. Astoria, NY, 241 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Richards Iron Works. Manitowoc, WI, 242 (Reel 22)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, Local 386 et al. v. St. Louis Coffin. St. Louis, MO., 243 (Reel 22)
  - Leadburners v. Du Pont Powder. Hopewell, VA, 244 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Galveston Wharf. Galveston, TX, 245 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Atlantic Elevator et al. Minneapolis, MN., 246 (Reel 22)
  - Employers Association v. Union Carpenters. Poughkeepsie, NY, 247 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Quincy Railway. Quincy, IL, 248 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, District 77 v. Minneapolis Threshing Machine. Hopkins, MN, 249 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 764 v. Kansas City Railway. Kansas City, MO, 250 (Reel 22)
  - Kansas City Railways' Employees v. Kansas City Railway. Kansas City, MO, 251 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 770 v. Mobile Light and Railway. Mobile, AL, 252 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 199 v. Ottumwa Railway. Ottumwa, IA, 253 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 198 v. Hedrick Construction. Dallas, TX, 254 (Reel 22)
  - Shipyard Timekeepers, Local 16164 v. Bethlehem Shipbuilding. Baltimore, MD, 255 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 381 v. Butte Electric Railway. Butte, MT, 256 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Tredegar Iron Works. Richmond, VA, 257 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Smith and Wesson. Springfield, MA., 258 (Reel 22)
  - Federal Labor Union 16087 et al. v. Walworth Manufacturing. Kewanee, IL., 259 (Reel 22)
  - Textile Workers v. Lorraine Mills et al. Pawtucket, RI., 260 (Reel 22)
  - Moran Towing et al. v. Board of Arbitration et al. New York City, 261 (Reel 22)
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, Local 547 v. Montana Flour Mill et al. Great Falls, MT, 262 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 669 and 737 v. Rochester and Syracuse Railway. Syracuse, NY, 263 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 580 v. Syracuse and Suburban Railway. Syracuse, NY, 264 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Waynesboro Street Railway. Waynesboro, PA, 265 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 421 v. Shamokin and Mt. Carmel Transit. Mt. Carmel, PA, 266 (Reel 22)
  - Locomotive Engineers, Locals 419 and 868 v. New York Consolidated Railway. New York City, NY, 267 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 62 v. Bass Foundry. Fort Wayne, IN, 268 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 797 v. Topeka Street Railway. Topeka, KS, 269 (Reel 22)
  - Messengers of American Railway Express v. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. La Junta, CO, 270 (Reel 22)
  - Fire Fighters Local 93 v. City of Cleveland. Cleveland, OH, 271 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Hudson Coal. Providence. RI, 272 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 681 and 737 v. Empire State Railroad. Syracuse, NY, 273 (Reel 22)
  - Hoisting Engineers v. Employers. Red Mountain, AL, 274 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Morrison Brothers et al. Dubuque, IA, 275 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Hatcher Tool. Detroit, MI, 276 (Reel 22)
  - Steam Fitters, Local 572 et al. v. Nashville Munition Plant. Nashville, TN., 277 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 441 v. Des Moines City Railway et al. Des Moines, IA, 278 (Reel 22)
  - Furnace Mens Unione 271 v. Adrian Furnace. Du Bois, PA, 279 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 759 v. Lima Street Railway. Lima, OH., 280 (Reel 22)
  - Timberworkers, Local 72 v. Blackwell Lumber. Coeur D'Alene, ID, 281 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Commercial Solvents. Terre Haute, IN, 282 (Reel 22)
  - United Mine Workers, Local 2050 v. Pittsburgh Coal. Pittsburgh, PA, 283 (Reel 22)
  - Textile Workers v. Swift Spinning Mills. Columbus, GA., 284 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 834 v. Columbus Street Railway. Columbus, GA., 285 (Reel 22)
  - Miners et al. v. Nevada Consolidated Copper. McGill, Ruth and Ely, NV., 286 (Reel 22)
  - Ivers v. Tubular Rivet and Stud. Quincy, MA, 287 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Woonsocket Rubber. Woonsocket, RI, 288 (Reel 22)
  - Classified Laborers v. Treasury Department. San Francisco, 289 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. American Can. Geneva, NY, 290 (Reel 22)
  - Williamson Brothers v. Union Organizers. New York City, 291 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters v. War Department. Washington DC, 292 (Reel 22)
  - Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators v. Theatrical Managers. Oklahoma City, OK, 293 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 558 v. Shreveport Railway. Shreveport, LA, 294 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 33 v. Price Electric. New Castle, PA, 295 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers v. Employers. Toledo, OH, 296 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Cosden Refinery. Tulsa, OK, 297 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners v. George W. Smith et al. Philadelphia, 298 (Reel 22)
  - Philadelphia Roll and Machine v. Molders Union. Philadelphia, PA, 299 (Reel 22)
  - Blacksmiths v. Watertown Arsenal. Watertown, MA, 300 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 12 v. Poole Engineering. Baltimore, MD, 301 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. A.H. Peterson Manufacturing. Milwaukee, WI., 302 (Reel 22)
  - Employees, Local 310 v. Hull and Dillon Packing. Pittsburg, KS, 303 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 829 v. Arkansas Valley Interurban Railway. Wichita, KS, 304 (Reel 22)
  - Elevator Operators and Starters, Local 495 v. Employers. San Francisco., 305 (Reel 22)
  - Meat Cutters and Butchers, Local 227 v. Armour. Louisville, KY, 306 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Standard Boiler and Plate Iron. Niles, OH, 307 (Reel 22)
  - James McCurrach v. Neckwear Cutters. New York City, 308 (Reel 22)
  - Miners' Union v. Maplewood Sales. Peoria, IL, 309 (Reel 22)
  - Workers v. National Car Coupler. Attica, IN, 310 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. McIntosh Seymour. Auburn, NY, 311 (Reel 22)
  - Painters and Paperhangers et al. v. Contracting Painters et al. San Diego, 312 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Third Avenue Railway. New York City, 313 (Reel 22)
  - Boilermakers, Local 127 v. Advance Rumley. Battle Creek, MI., 314 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Western Drop Forge. Marion, IN., 315 (Reel 22)
  - Foundry Employees, Local 66 et al. v. Bakers Manufacturing. Saratoga, NY, 316 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters and Joiners, Local 414 v. Government Powder Plant. Nashville, TN, 317 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Pittsfield Machine and Tool. Pittsfield, MA, 318 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. American Locomotive Works. Paterson, NJ, 319 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Niles-Bement-Pond. Plainfield, NJ, 320 (Reel 22)
  - Trades Council v. Employers. Bay City, MI, 321 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Scullin Steel. St. Louis, MO, 322 (Reel 22)
  - Marie Martin et al. v. Spang and Company. Butler, PA., 323 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 312 v. Tri-City Railway et al. Rock Island, IL, 324 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 313 v. Tri-City Railway et al. Davenport, IA, 325 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 599 v. Clinton, Davenport and Muscatine Railway. Muscatine, IA, 326 (Reel 22)
  - Building Trades Council v. Government Shipbuilding Contractors. Miami, FL, 327 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. American Bronze. Berwyn, PA, 328 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 752 v. Bloomington and Normal Railway. Bloomington, IL, 329 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 277 v. Niles-Bement-Pond et al. Ridgway, PA., 330 (Reel 22)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers, Local 29 v. San Francisco Publishers Association. San Francisco, 331 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 85 v. Pittsburgh Railway. Pittsburgh, PA, 332 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 118 v. Eastern Pennsylvania Railway. Pottsville, PA, 333 (Reel 22)
  - Request of Ohio Electric Railway on Proposed Wage Scale. Cincinnati, OH, 334 (Reel 22)
  - Molders v. Hyde Windlass. Bath, ME, 335 (Reel 22)
  - Molders v. Hyde Windlass. Bath, ME, 336 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 183 v. Employers. Williamsport PA, 337 (Reel 22)
  - Delbert Horton v. Wilson Body. Bay City, MI, 338 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Pacific Coast Steel. Seattle, WA, 339 (Reel 22)
  - Firemen v. City Government. Kansas City, Missouri, 340 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 70 et al. v. Foundrymen's Association. Boston., 341 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Thomas Iron Works. Allentown, PA, 342 (Reel 22)
  - Plumbers Division v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC, 343 (Reel 22)
  - Printing Pressmen's Union 1 v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC, 344 (Reel 22)
  - Steamfitters v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC, 345 (Reel 22)
  - Painters v. US Government Printing Office. Washington, DC, 346 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters v. Frank Amman Construction. N.A, 347 (Reel 22)
  - Foremen, Machinists et al. v. Niagara Falls Power. Niagara Falls, NY, 348 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 343 v. Kern Mutual Telephone et al. Taft, CA., 349 (Reel 22)
  - Demands of United Mine Workers, District 1, 350 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Hartford Screw Company. Hartford, CT, 351 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 398 v. Wolfe Company et al. Chambersburg, PA, 352 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Rock Island Southern Railroad. Galesburg, IL, 353 (Reel 22)
  - Plasterers v. Builders Exchange. St. Paul, MN, 354 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Pinkney Mining. Russellville, AL., 355 (Reel 22)
  - United Mine Workers, Locals 957, 599, and 1167 v. Sandor Engle. Glenlyon, PA, 356 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Emerson Brantingham. Rockford, IL, 357 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Nordberg Manufacturing. Milwaukee, WI, 358 (Reel 22)
  - Watch Service Department v. Pullman. Pullman, IL, 359 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Union Salt. Cleveland, OH, 360 (Reel 22)
  - Railway Express Drivers, Local 720 v. Railway Express. Chicago, 361 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Oklahoma Street Railway. Oklahoma City, OK, 362 (Reel 22)
  - Employees of Distribution Department v. Public Service Gas. Camden, NJ., 363 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 420 v. Elkhart Iron Works et al. Elkhart, IN., 364 (Reel 22)
  - Cigar Makers v. Pollock Company. Wheeling, WV, 365 (Reel 22)
  - Pattern Makers v. Starr Piano et al. Richmond, IN, 366 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. United Zinc Smelting. Moundsville, WV, 367 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Hoyt White Metal. Granite City, IL., 368 (Reel 22)
  - Retort House Men v. Peoples Gas and Electric. Oswego, NY, 369 (Reel 22)
  - Metal Trades Council v. Anaconda Copper. Butte, MT, 370 (Reel 22)
  - Allied Shoe Workers v. Employers. Haverhill, MA, 371 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Studebaker Corporation. Detroit, MI, 372 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists v. Sturtevant. Hyde Park, MA, 373 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Utah-Idaho Central Railway. Eureka, UT, 374 (Reel 22)
  - Baggage men et al. v. Consolidated Express. Indianapolis, 375 (Reel 22)
  - Blacksmiths v. Bedford Stone Club. Bedford, IN., 376 (Reel 22)
  - City Fire Fighters, Local 22 v. City of Philadelphia, 377 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Leeds and Northrup. Philadelphia, 378 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Local 1 v. J.G. Brill et al. Philadelphia, 379 (Reel 22)
  - Discharged Employees v. Bethlehem Steel. North Lebanon, PA., 380 (Reel 22)
  - Trainmen v. Ohio Valley Electric Railway. Huntington, WV, 381 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 417 v. Baker Manufacturing et al. Saratoga Springs, NY., 382 (Reel 22)
  - Typographical Union 16 v. American Newspaper Publishers. Chicago., 383 (Reel 22)
  - Conductors and Motormen v. Michigan United Railways. Jackson, MI, 384 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Buick. Flint, MI, 385 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati, Lawrenceburg, and Aurora Electric Railway. Cincinnati, OH, 386 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati Traction. Cincinnati, OH., 387 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 627 v. Cincinnati and Columbus Traction. Cincinnati, OH, 388 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 631 v. Cincinnati, Milford and Loveland Traction Company. Cincinnati, OH, 389 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Conestoga Traction. Lancaster, PA, 390 (Reel 22)
  - Blacksmiths, Local 455 v. Evansville Tool Works. Evansville, IN., 391 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 831 v. Louisville Street Railway et al. Louisville, KY, 392 (Reel 22)
  - Tin, Sheet Iron, and Granite Workers, Union 10943 v. National Enameling and Stamping. Granite City, IL, 393 (Reel 22)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers v. Reading iron. Reading and Danville, PA, 394 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Eastern Steel. Pottsville, PA, 395 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Bethlehem Steel. North Lebanon, PA, 396 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters District Council v. Fabricated Ship. Milwaukee, WI, 397 (Reel 22)
  - Request of Tennessee Federation of Labor for Investigation at Old Hickory Powder Plant. Knoxville, TN, 398 (Reel 22)
  - Carpenters v. War Department. Dayton, OH, 399 (Reel 22)
  - Asbestos Workers v. Stuart McGehee Construction. Camp Pike, AR, 400 (Reel 22)
  - Union Painters v. St. Louis Waterproofing. Urbana and Champaign, IL, 401 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Inland Ordnance et al. Bedford, OH, 402 (Reel 22)
  - Bricklayers v. American Car and Foundry. Berwick, PA, 403 (Reel 22)
  - Drop Forge Trades v. Billings and Spencer et al. Hartford, CT, 404 (Reel 22)
  - Machinists, Lodge 812 v. Knight Manufacturing. NA, 405 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 714 v. Cumberland County Power and Light. Portland, ME, 406 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Danville Street Railway. Danville, Il, 407 (Reel 22)